<resources>
    <string name="app_name">VARANASI TOUR </string>
    <string name="sign_out">Sign Out</string>

    <string name="ramnagar">RamNagar Fort</string>
    <string name="ramnagar1">The Ramnagar Fort is a fortification in Ramnagar, Varanasi, India. It is located near the Ganga River on its eastern bank, opposite to the Tulsi Ghat. The sandstone structure was built in the Mughal style in 1750 by Kashi Naresh Raja Balwant Singh. </string>

    <string name="Manikarnika">Manikarnika Ghat</string>
    <string name="Manikarnika1">Manikarnika Ghat (Hindi: मणिकर्णिका घाट) is one of the holiest among the sacred riverfronts (ghats), alongside the river Ganga. It is believed that a dead human\'s soul finds salvation (moksha), when cremated here. Thus, scores of the elderly across the whole country seek to walk up to its edges, and spend their last days absorbing the charisma of the ghat - which makes even death painless and insignificant to be pondered upon.

     </string>

    <string name="kashitemple">Shri Kashi Vishwanath Temple</string>
    <string name="kashitemple1">
        Kashi Vishvanath Temple is one of the most famous Hindu temples dedicated to Lord Shiva. It is located in Varanasi, Uttar Pradesh, India. The temple stands on the western bank of the holy river Ganga, and is one of the twelve Jyotirlingas, the holiest of Shiva temples. The main deity is known by the name Vishvanatha or Vishveshvara meaning Ruler of The Universe.
    </string>


    <string name="Darbhanga">Darbhaga Ghat</string>
    <string name="Darbhanga1">This is an other ghat of kashi that we pass through as we boat along ganga. Birds from Algeria often visit the ghats during nov-Dec</string>

    <string name="Panchganga">Panchganga Ghat</string>
    <string name="Panchganga1">Panchganga Ghat is the place where five sacred rivers converge to form an overwhelming spectacle of beauty and holiness. The five holy rivers are the Ganges, Saraswati, Yamuna, Kirana and Dhupapapa.

The Panchganga Ghat stands as an example of Hindu-Muslim harmony. The Mosque of Alamgir, also known as Beni Madhav-ka-Darera, stands tall near the ghat on a site where it is believed stood the Bindu Madhava Temple.</string>


    <string name="River">River Ganges</string>
    <string name="River1">The river is considered sacred and holds religious significance. So, it is worshipped by the Hindus. The Ganges is originated from the Gangotri and has many temples settled along its banks. Varanasi, being situated on the banks of River Ganges is regarded as the most holy city of India.</string>

    <string name="Bhu">BHU</string>
    <string name="Bhu1">Banaras Hindu University (Hindi: [kaʃi hind̪u viʃvəvid̪yaləy], BHU), formerly Central Hindu College, is a public central university located in Varanasi, Uttar Pradesh. It was established in 1916 by Madan Mohan Malaviya.[2] With over 30,000 students residing in campus, it claims the title of largest residential university in Asia.[3]

The university's main campus spread over 1,300 acres (5.3 km2) was built on land donated by the Kashi Naresh, the hereditary ruler of Banaras ("Kashi" being an alternative name for Banaras or Varanasi).</string>

    <string name="Statue">Statue of Standing Buddha</string>
    <string name="Statue1">The 80 ft high statue of Buddha. It isIndia’s tallest standing statue of Lord Buddha. It took 14 years to contruct this statue. The work on the statue was started in 1997 and it was unveiled in 2011. This standing statue of Buddha is located on the premises of Thai Buddha Vihar in Sarnath.
This 80-ft Buddha statue made from sandstone is a result of joint efforts between India and Thailand. The standing statue of Lord Buddha is built over an area of 2.5 acre inside the premises of Thai Buddha Vihar (earlier known as Mrigdayavan Mahavihar Society).</string>

    <string name="sarnath">Sarnath</string>
    <string name="sarnath1">Sarnath is a place located 10 kilometres north-east of Varanasi near the confluence of the Ganges and the Varuna rivers in Uttar Pradesh, India. The deer park in Sarnath is where Gautama Buddha first taught the Dhamma, and where the Buddhist Sangha came into existence through the enlightenment of Kondanna.</string>

    <string name="Chunar">Chunar Fort</string>
    <string name="Chunar1">The Chunar Fort (also known as Chandrakanta Chunargarh and Charanadri) is located in Mirzapur district of Uttar Pradesh, in India. Along with Chunar town, situated below the fort, the two are historic places with common history and legends.[1] It is located 14 miles (23 km) south west of Varanasi.</string>

    <string name="mary">St. Mary\'s Church</string>
    <string name="mary1">Varanasi is a cauldron of different cultures and religions, Hinduism being the dominant flavour. But you can find other places of worship apart from the beautiful Hindu temples. St. Mary’s Church is famous for its distinct louvered doors and hooded ventilation. The church has a beautiful design with a projecting portico.</string>


    <string name="Bharat">Bharat Mata Temple</string>
    <string name="Bharat1">Bharat Mata Mandir (meaning "Mother India Temple") is located on the Mahatma Gandhi Kashi Vidyapith campus in Varanasi, India. Instead of traditional statues of gods and goddesses, this temple has a huge map of undivided India carved in marble. This temple is dedicated to Bharat Mata and claims to be the only one of its kind in the world.</string>


    <string name="Annapurna">Shri Annapurna Restaurant,Banquet And Sweet Shop</string>
    <string name="Annapurna1">Basic vegetarian cafe with a menu listing north and south Indian, thali, Asian and Continental food.
         Address: Shop No. J-12/16-A, Ramkatora, Near Sunbeam Dalims, Varanasi, Uttar Pradesh 221001
         Hours:
         Open 9:30AM⋅ Closes 10:30PM
          Phone: 092355 96416</string>

    <string name="varanasi">Varanasi Cafe And Bakery Restaurant</string>
    <string name="varanasi1"> There are so many yummy items on the menu. This bakery/restaurant also specializes in serving different types of cheeses. Also offered are Indian cuisine, a full breakfast menu, sandwiches, pasta, pizzas, salads, appetizers, teas and coffee, lassie and shakes, and smoothies to name a few. Make a stop here if you're in the area, the food is worth it!!!</string>

    <string name="canton">Canton Royale Restaurant</string>
    <string name="canton1">Canton Royale Restaurant is known for its great food and reasonable prices along with the large collection of drinks. It is an oasis for famished, thirsty travelers who are looking for a great meal with relaxing drinks. This place, with its calm ambiance and attentive staff members, offers a delightful experience. An in-house restaurant at Hotel Surya, Canton Royale Restaurant is a great place to dine-in. Exuding colonial elegance from its 200-year-old heritage building, this place has a charm incomparable to any other, in Varanasi. A mug of beer can be accompanied with Goat Cheese, Paneer Spinach, and Chicken Kebabs here. The pizzas are scrumptious, and the Mexican Fajitas are a must-try. </string>

    <string name="ganpati">Ganpati Restaurant</string>

    <string name="ganpati1">For the vegetarians in Varanasi, Ganpati Restaurant is just the right place. Enjoy a full meal here, complete with thirst-quenching beverages. Drool over the vegetarian preparations and treat your taste buds and tummy, heartily. Gorge on the delicious preparations with sheer delight at this wonderful place that offers a great outdoor seating arrangement too. The view of Varanasi is amazing, and you can soak in the spiritual air of the city while enjoying a scrumptious meal. Offering Indian meal as well as Chinese and Continental food, this place attracts the local crowd as well the tourists. The prices are reasonable. The must-try items are Mixed Veg and Paneer Butter Masala with Naan.</string>


    <string name="newkashi">New Vishwanath Temple</string>
    <string name="newkashi1">There are an OLD and a NEW Vishwanath Temple in Varanasi. New Vishwanath Temple has been made in BHU Campus.The temple made by white marbles and the beauty of the architecture have ability to amaze you for sure this is new temple of lord Shiva but you can feel the peace and inside happiness when you inside this temple</string>

    <string name="bharatkala">Bharat Kala Bhavan</string>
    <string name="bharatkala1">Bharat Kala Bhavan (Hindi: भारत कला भवन) is an art and archeological museum located in Banaras Hindu University, Varanasi, India. It has been instrumental in collecting art and is one the important touristic attractions in the Banaras Hindu University and in Varanasi city.</string>

    <string name="chaukhandi">Chaukhandi Stupa</string>
    <string name="chaukhandi1">Chaukhandi Stupa is an important Buddhist stupa in Sarnath, located 8 kilometres from Cantt Railway Station Varanasi, Uttar Pradesh, India. Stupas have evolved from burial mounds and serve as a shrine for a relic of the Buddha.</string>

    <string name="gyanvapi">Gyanvapi Mosque</string>
    <string name="gyanvapi1">The Gyanvapi mosque is located in Varanasi, Uttar Pradesh, India. It was constructed by the Mughal Emperor Aurangzeb. It is located north of Dashashwamedh Ghat, near Lalita Ghat along the river Ganga.

It is a Jama Masjid located in the heart of the Varanasi city. It is administered by Anjuman Inthazamiya Masajid (AIM).</string>


</resources>
